Ima Joy Chodorow Gandler Texas Jewish collection, Inclusive: 1827-2009, undated, Bulk: 1972-2004
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- General, 1924-1996; 5
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 5, Block 2, Woodlake Addition, City of Waco (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 5, Block 2, Woodlake Addition, City of Waco (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Abstract of Title: Lot 5, Block 2, Woodlake Addition, City of Waco (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Child Welfare, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Correspondence, 1962-1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Crime, Greater Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Jacob de Cordova, 1968-1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Juvenile Group Homes, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Juvenile Group Homes, 1977-1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Juvenile Group Homes, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Jim Hightower, Texas Agriculture Commissioner, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, Lists, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, Planning, 1981-1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, 1994-1996 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco High School Class of 1941 Reunion, Planning, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco Human Rights Committee (1 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco Human Rights Committee (2 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco State Home (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Archie Hoppenstein: Waco State Home (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Senior Citizen Centers, 1978-1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Lena Lynn: American Legion Auxiliary, 1959-1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Lena Lynn: Jolly Huaco Grandmother’s Club, Membership, 1963-1966 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Lena Lynn: Jolly Huaco Grandmother’s Club, Program and Directories, 1967-1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Properties: Lot 10, Block 2, Woodlake Addition, City of Waco, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Properties: Lots 2-10 and 12-19, Westview Addition Part 2, City of Waco, 1979-1981 (Box 45, Folder 12)